霍华德·沃罗威茨
Howard Wolowitz.
霍华德  我是太空总署的戴夫·罗杰
Hey, Howard. Dave Roeger here at NASA.
我们需要谈谈你接下来的任务
We need to talk about your upcoming mission.
没问题  我每天都还有在做俯卧撑呢
Yes, yes, I've been doing my push-ups.
虽然我目前只能做九个  但...
I'm still stuck at nine, but...
这都是没人托着我的情况下顺利完成的
...that's going all the way down with no one holding me.
那很好  但这不是我找你的原因
That's great, uh, but that's not why I called.
我们遇到点大麻烦
We've run into a bit of a snafu.
你的联盟号太空舱没通过增压测试
Your Soyuz capsule failed the pressurization test,
总而言之  你的任务被废止了
so bottom line, mission's been scrubbed.
不是吧  那"废止"的意思是...
You're kidding. So what does that mean?
我不得不说
Boy, I got to tell you,
我真的很失望
I'm really disappointed.
这是我儿时以来的梦想
This was my dream ever since I was a little kid.
无论如何  还是要感谢您的来电
Okay, well, uh,  thanks for the call.
好的  您也保重
Yep, you, too.
太棒了  谢天谢地啊
Yes! Thank you!
老子不用死在太空里了
I'm not gonna die in space!
我可以按照上帝的旨意
I'm gonna die the way God intended,
五六十岁时  死于吃太多熏肉引发的心脏病了
in my late 50s, with a heart full of pastrami.
生活大爆炸第五季第二十三集
我需要一件更大的衬衫
I'm going to need a larger shirt.
这件腋下部位有点紧
This one's a little tight under the arms.
好吧
Okay.
你不觉得之所以会紧
Do you think maybe it's tight
是因为你里面穿了套长的内衣裤吗
because you're wearing long underwear?
废话  当然是因为这个
Yes, of course that's why it's tight.
好吧  让我重新表述下问题
All right, let me rephrase the question.
你干嘛要穿长的内衣裤啊
Why are you wearing long underwear?
你不是吧
You're kidding.
重点应该是  "为何你不穿长内衣裤"
Shouldn't the question be: why aren't you?
不  应该是"为何你穿啊"
No, it should be: why are you?
莱纳德  这些租赁的礼服早已被
Leonard, these rental tuxedos have been
上百个满身臭汗的陌生人穿过
worn by hundreds of sweaty strangers.
我连沾到自己的汗都讨厌
I don't like my own sweat touching my skin,
陌生人的汗不是更要命吗
how do you think I feel about theirs?
试试这件吧
Why don't you slip this on?
就跟绞刑吏来送绞索一样
Said the hangman offering a noose.
虽然不如他租保龄球鞋时搞笑
Well, that wasn't as entertaining as when he rents bowling shoes,
不过也相差无几了
but it was right up there.
好吧  木已成舟
Well, that's it.
我的任命被撤销了
My orders have been rescinded.
我正式"去不成"太空了
I am officially "no go" to space.
我很遗憾  霍华德  不过老实说
I'm sorry, Howard, but I got to tell you,
你去不成  我反倒松了一口气
I'm a little relieved you're not going.
为什么
Why?
拜托  送你上太空的火箭
Come on, you were gonna go up in a rocket
可是俄国人在上世纪六十年代设计的
designed in the 1960s by the Russians.
是啊  那又如何
Yeah, so?
你可有过去百思买购物时
When was the last time you were at Best Buy
听别人说  "快看这个蓝光播放器
and you heard someone say, "ooh, check out this Blu-ray player,
是俄国制造的呢  肯定不错"的经验吗
it must be good, it was built in Russia"?
他们的技术也没那么糟啦
Well, their technology isn't that bad.
当你坐着联盟号太空舱返回地球时
When you come back to Earth in a Soyuz capsule,
你会以每小时500英里的速度自由落体
you free-fall from space at 500 miles per hour,
唯一帮你减速的东西
and the only thing that slows you down
是你撞向地面的前一刻
is a little parachute that pops out
弹出的小小降落伞
right before you crash into the ground.
而设计这火箭的人  可是连飞鼠洛奇和
And the whole thing was designed by the same brilliant minds
驯鹿布尔温克都抓不到的"聪明"俄国人呢
who were unable to capture Rocky and Bullwinkle.
飞鼠洛奇和驯鹿布尔温克
美国六十年代经典卡通片《飞鼠洛基冒险记》的主角
好吧  不管怎么说
All right, well, whatever.
我一点也不担心
I wasn't worried.
是吗
You weren't?
让我解释一下你和我的区别
Let me explain the difference between you and me.
你是《星际迷航》的看客
You watch Star Trek
而我是住客
I live it.
拜托  《星际迷航》可有过任何一集
Oh, please. I don't remember the episode of Star Trek
是讲一个没去成太空的家伙
where the guy never goes to space
在礼服店自吹自擂的故事啊
and brags about it in a tuxedo store.
随你怎么嘲笑我
Make all the jokes you want,
但我们之中  也就只有一个人足够勇敢
but there's only one of us here brave enough
差点真做了上太空的大业
to almost do what I almost did.
这回好多了
Ah, much better.
你现在肯定热得要死吧
You must be burning up.
是有点  不过也比你们从那些裤子染上点
A little. But not more than your urethras will be
不知名的病菌  然后尿道灼热瘙痒来得强
after whatever's in those pants swims up them.
我将潇洒与卫生完美的结合起来了  不是吗
I cut quite the dashing, yet hygienic figure, don't I?
我看上去就像是闪电侠要结婚了
I look like the Flash about to get married.
天啊  废纸巾  废纸巾
Oh! A tissue! A tissue!
上帝啊
Oh, good Lord!
他要上哪去
Uh, where's he going?
他在车里准备了紧急消毒液
He keeps emergency Purell in the car.
钥匙给我 给我  给我
Keys! Keys! Keys!
-是你啊  -我进来之前
- Hey, you. - Before I come in,
得先告诉你  我可是有"气"而来哟
you should know, I have gas.
说起来  你还说过更烂的开场白呢
For the record, not your worst opening line.
来看吧  这瓶气是我用来让
Check it out. It's the gas I use
自由电子激光支持高电压的
in my free-electron laser to support high voltages.
但它还有个有趣的第二用途
But it also has an interesting secondary use.
给你  吸一口
Here. Breathe this in.
在我吸之前
B-Before I do it,
如果你是条子  你会告诉我的吧
if you're a cop you have to tell me, right?
-吸就好啦  -好吧
- Just try it. - Okay.
吸完后会...
What's it supposed to...
天啊  这太诡异了
Oh, my God, that's so freaky!
"你这个小气鬼"
You're a mean one
出自同名歌曲《You're a mean one, Mr. Grinch》
"圣诞怪杰先生"
Mr. Grinch.
好了好了  到我了  准备好没
Okay. Me, me, me. Ready?
莱纳德  我是你爹
Leonard, I am your father.
我这辈子从没这么被一个
I have never been more attracted to a woman
声音像男人的女人吸引过
who sounds like a man in my life.
你知道我们一直...
Hey... you know how we've been...
进展得比较慢吧
taking things slow?
我最近一直在想...
Well, I've been thinking, and...
或许我准备好...
maybe I'm ready to...
让进展加快...一点点啦
take things a little... faster.
太好了
Oh, great.
我向你保证  憋了四个月之后
And I promise, after waiting four months,
也就只能当"快枪手"了
fast is what you're gonna get.
不过有个问题
You know, just-just one thing.
我们现在关系那么融洽
Look, we're in a really great place right now,
我不想做出任何
and I don't want to do anything
把关系弄尴尬的事情
that will make stuff all weird again.
那我们就别让它变尴尬不得了
So we won't let it get weird.
行  我还得提个醒
Okay. Oh, and just a heads-up...
从我们上次"亲密"到现在这之间
mm, since the last time you saw me naked,
儿童节目《芝麻街》中的人物角色
我纹了个甜怪饼纹身
I got a Cookie Monster tattoo.
你看到的时候  除了称赞"好炫"
The acceptable response"s when you see it
我不想听到其他废话
are "awesome" or nothing.
那我就说
What about...
我要甜饼
Cookies!
艾米
Amy?
七点  刚好准时
7:00, right on time.
这可不是什么"刚好"
It's not an accident.
人家在足足在门外等了二十分钟呢
I waited outside your door for 20 minutes.
晚餐马上就好
Well, dinner's almost ready.
我不得不说
I must say,
我真没想到你会选择在家里
I was surprised you chose to spend
度过我们的约会之夜
our date night in your apartment.
正如我提到的
As I mentioned,
帕萨迪纳市议会正在辩论加长行人过马路的时间
the Pasadena City Council is debating longer crosswalk times,
而且  乐高专卖店午夜还会举行疯狂大甩卖
and later, the LEGO store is having a midnight madness sale.
任谁都觉得那样的约会更血脉喷张
You ask anyone, that's a hot date.
是挺诱人  不过今晚我准备了
Tempting choices, but I have something special
一些特别的东西
planned for tonight.
有什么能比
What can be more special than
在去买乐高夺宝奇兵模型的路上
having an adequate amount of time to cross the street
能有充足时间过马路更特别啊
on your way to buy a tiny LEGO Indiana Jones?
鉴于我们的朋友  关系都正在向前发展
With our friends moving forward in their relationships,
我决定我们的关系也该更进一步了
I've decided that we should make progress in ours as well.
老天哪
Oh, dear Lord.
两年前我们还不认识对方呢
Two years ago, we didn't even know each other,
现在我们就"夜晚时分你家见"了
and now I'm in your apartment after dark.
这关系进展得还不够快吗
How much faster can this thing go?
我早有预感你会不同意
I had a feeling you'd be reluctant,
所以我准备要使出我
which is why I'm going to dip
神经生物学版的锦囊妙计了
into my neurobiological bag of tricks.
你那些猴子主意最好玩了  挖吧
Oh, you brain monkeys kill me. Dip away.
我设计了一个实验
I have devised an experiment
我相信这能让你
that I believe will increase your feelings for me
加快对我产生感情
in an accelerated time frame.
你准备怎么做呢
And how do you propose to do that?
希望你不是想着
Uh, hope you're not thinking
用迷幻药来对我进行思想控制
about some sort of LSD thought control.
因为我只喜欢一种迷药  此药名"知识"
Because there's only one mind-expanding drug that this man enjoys,
"唯知识能令我着迷"
and that's called school.
情感的依赖是随着人类生长而诞生的
Human beings form emotional attachments as they grow up.
以你来说  你依恋母亲  超能英雄等等
In your case, to your mother, superheroes, et cetera.
我准备尝试一个实验
I'm going to attempt an experiment that
让你将这些情感转移到我身上
will get you to transfer those feelings to me.
看来今晚的菜
Well, seems what's on the menu tonight
只有"胡言乱语"和"胡说八道"呢
is malarkey with a big side of poppycock.
试了才知道
We'll see.
我们先听一首浪漫的晚餐音乐  好吗
Let's start with a little romantic dinner music, shall we?
超级玛丽的主题曲
Super Mario Bros.theme?
没错
Yes.
我明白你在干什么了
I see what you're doing.
你想如法炮制艾宾豪斯的方法
You're attempting to build on the work of Ebbinghaus
德国心理学家  首先设计了测量机械学习和记忆的实验方法
证实了记忆是基于联想
从潜意识勾起我玩这个游戏时的记忆
by triggering an involuntary memory of me playing that game--
也就是我儿时那最快乐的六百个小时
admittedly the happiest 600 hours of my childhood...
不过这是没用的
...but it won't work.
好吧  但也不影响我们享用晚餐
Fine. There's no reason we still can't have a lovely dinner.
你先就坐吧
Why don't you have a seat.
我给你倒点饮料喝吧
May I offer you something to drink?
你知道我不喝饮料
You know I don't drink.
这个也不喝吗
Not even...
草莓速溶奶
strawberry Quik?
我超爱草莓速溶奶
I love strawberry Quik.
我最喜欢的粉色液体
It's my favorite pink fluid,
比佩托比斯摩[粉色液体胃药]略胜一筹
narrowly beating out Pepto-Bismol.
我知道
Oh, I know.
我觉得这个正好搭配
I think it will go nicely
我特意准备的
with what I have prepared...
晚餐
for dinner.
意粉  里面还加了热狗切片
Spaghetti with little pieces of hot dog cut up in it!
跟以前你妈妈做的一样
Just like your mommy used to make.
大餐啊大餐
Oh... yummy, yummy!
我们以后要经常这样约会
We should do this more often.
糟糕
Uh-oh.
对不起  我错了
I'm sorry. I did,
我太过分了  我不是故意的
I crossed a line. I didn't mean to!
有谁会在做爱的时候说这样的话啊
Who says something like that right in the middle of sex?!
我不知道  不自觉就说出口了
I don't know, it just came out.
很多人在做爱期间都会说奇怪的话嘛
People say weird things during sex all the time.
可没人会说这个啊
Okay, well, they sure as hell don't say that.
-高潮时刻  情不自禁嘛  -放屁
- It was the heat of the moment. - No,
高潮时刻应该是说"对  太爽了"
the heat of the moment is, "Ooh, yeah, just like that,"
而不是说"你愿意嫁给我吗"
not "will you marry me?"
对不起
I'm sorry.
再给我一次机会吧
Just-just give me another chance.
好让你下次能有机会在滚床单时说
Why, so you can crawl under the covers and go,
"宝贝  想去看看
"Hey, baby, want to go look for houses
在好学校学区里的房子吗"
in neighborhoods with good schools?"
我还是那句话  对不起
Again, I'm sorry.
你也知道  霍华德和伯纳黛特要结婚了
You know, with Howard and Bernadette getting married,
我被这股结婚热感染了
I got caught up in a little wedding fever.
我收回那句话
I take it back.
这种话覆水难收啊
You can't take something like that back.
我们现在该如何是好
I mean, what are we even supposed to do now?
说不定将来  某天回想起
Okay, at some point, we'll look back
会觉得这其实挺搞笑的啊
and this is going to be a funny story.
我们现在就可以当笑话看嘛
Why don't we just start doing that now?
-你不是吧  -我是说真的
- You're kidding. - No.
你还记不记得
Hey, do you remember...
我在床上向你求婚的那件事啊
...that time when I proposed to you in bed?
你当时一脸惊讶  说"你说毛呢"
And you were all, like, "What are you doing?"
真是笑死人了
That was so funny.
太好笑了
So funny.
一点都不好笑
It's not funny.
让笑点再酝酿一会
Give it a minute.
嘴角是不是要扬起微笑啦
Is that a little smile I see there?
我还是闪吧
I should go.
我刚刚在想
Hey, I was thinking.
我们结婚时的第一支舞蹈
For our first dance at the wedding,
我们学电影《辣身舞》里的最后那支舞怎么样
what if we learn the final number from Dirty Dancing?
-你说笑的吧  -说真的
- You're kidding. - No,
来嘛
come on.
那该有多酷啊
How cool would that be?
我奔向你的臂弯
Me running into your arms...
你把我举在空中
you lifting me up into the air.
某人心情不错呀
Oh, you're in a good mood.
当然啦  有什么好不开心的
Yeah, well, why wouldn't I be?
我就要迎娶我的梦中情人了
You know, I'm marrying the girl of my dreams,
而且我也终于说服我妈
and I finally got my mother to agree
不跟着咱们去度蜜月了
not to come on our honeymoon.
是航空航天局打来的
Oh, it's NASA.
我是沃罗威茨
Wolowitz.
戴夫  怎么了
Oh! Hi, Dave. What's up?
你没开玩笑吧  真的吗
No kidding. Really?
这  这真是太好了
Well, that's...great news.
天大的好消息
Great, great news.
好的  我会查邮件的
All right, I'll watch my e-mail for the details.
好的  回头聊
Okay, talk soon.
什么天大的好消息呀
What's so great?
看来我还是要上太空了
It looks like I'm going into space after all.
华仔  这太棒了
Oh, Howie, that's wonderful!
是挺棒
Uh-huh, wonderful.
怎么回事  他们不是把你的任务取消了吗
What happened? I thought they canceled your mission.
是取消了
Th-They did.
可是航空航天局很想把我的望远镜装上太空站
But NASA really wants my telescope up on the space station,
所以他们要让我提前升空
so they're putting me on an earlier launch.
-什么时候  -下周五
- When?  - A...week from Friday.
什么  可咱们的婚礼就在那个周日呀
What? We're getting married that Sunday.
说的没错
You're right!
我  我不能去太空
I-I can't go to space.
我要结婚
I have to get married,
这个理由没人能反驳
and no one can say that's not a good reason.
我这就打回给他
I'll call him back.
等一下  我不想成为阻碍你的那个人
Wait. I don't want to be the one who stands in your way.
可惜  你已经是了  米已成炊了
Well, too bad, you already did. It's a done deal.
但是没关系  我原谅你
Oh, well. But I forgive you.
不行  我不想这么开始咱们的婚姻
No. That's not how I want to start our marriage,
我怎么能一上来就毁掉你的梦想呢
killing your dream?
等你回来咱们再举办婚礼
We'll have the wedding when you get back.
可是我们已经做好计划而且喜帖都发了呀
But wh-what about all the plans and the guests?
打电话给大家取消就是了
We'll call them.
虽然我老爸会因为损失了酒席押金
Although my dad's gonna go a little nutso
而不是太爽
over losing his deposits.
没错  他一定会的
You're right, he is!
你爸会气疯的
Your dad's gonna be furious.
他不可能会同意我们延迟婚礼
There's no way he's gonna let us postpone this wedding.
至少咱们努力过了
Well, we tried.
我去跟他谈
I'll talk to him.
他不会拒绝他的宝贝女儿的
He won't say no to his little girl.
不  应该我去跟他谈
No! I-I should talk to him,
来场男人跟男人间的对话
man to man.
但是  华仔  我老爸很凶的
But, Howie, my dad can be a bully.
他会逼你  不让你上太空的
He's gonna make you cancel your space flight.
这样最好...
We can only hope...
是别发生啦
that he doesn't.
象挪到二层的
Bishop to queen four,
四号皇后
level two.
将军
Check.
谢尔顿
Sheldon...
马吃掉象
knight takes bishop.
你没事吧
You all right?
我没事
I'm fine.
真的吗
Are you?
你把你的皇后暴露在敌军之中
You left your queen exposed from above,
把你的马困在了角落里
you trapped your knight in the corner,
还不停地一边叹气一边说"为什么是我"
and you keep sighing and saying, "Why me?"
好吧
Very well.
我能问你一个关于女人的问题吗
Can I ask you a question about women?
我们去年不是买了那本书给你嘛
We got you that book last year.
那里面的东西还不够全面吗
Wasn't everything in there?
不是  我跟艾米有点感情问题
No, I'm having a relationship problem with Amy.
顺便说一句  我看完那本书就做噩梦
And by the way, that book gave me nightmares.
我跟佩妮最近也闹得很僵
Well, if it makes you feel any better,
也许这样能让你觉得好受点
I screwed things up pretty good with Penny.
你看咱俩现在  莱纳德
Look at us, Leonard...
都会像普通的男人一样
engaging in the social convention of
聚在一起抱怨自己家的女人了
men bellyaching about their ol' ladies.
是啊
I guess we are.
那说说吧  你们怎么了
So, what's going on?
信不信由你
Believe it or not,
艾米开始想尽办法哄我开心
Amy has embarked on a campaign
就为了增进
to increase my feelings for her
我对她的感情
by making me happy.
我深表同情  你肯定觉得"很不好受"
I'm sorry, that must be very difficult for you.
简直糟透了
It's awful.
今早  她替我打点好一切
This morning, she arranged for me
让我当一天全美铁路客运公司的小售票员
to be an Amtrak junior conductor for the day.
通常  这种机会只提供给小孩子
It-It's usually only open to children.
她逼人家为我破例了
She got them to make an exception.
她真无耻
Shame on her.
他们让我吹哨子了  莱纳德
They let me blow the whistle, Leonard.
她还真有两下子
She's good.
就是啊  而且事态愈发严重了
I know. And it gets worse.
她的努力已经开始让我
Her efforts are causing me
在不恰当的时候
to have affectionate feelings for her
对她想入非非了
at inappropriate times.
你是指在床上或是在你冲凉的时候吗
You mean, like in bed or in the shower?
才不是呢
No!
你能别再引用那本万恶淫书中的句子了吗
Would you please stop referencing that infernal book?
比如说  今天早上
For example, this morning,
我正在计算真空条件下虚粒子的
I was calculating the random motion
无规则运动
of virtual particles in a vacuum,
突然间那些虚粒子
when suddenly the particles morphed
变形成了艾米的头皮屑
into an image of Amy's dandruff...
慢慢地从她的头上倾泻而下
...gently cascading down onto her pale,
落在她苍白又微微隆起的肩膀上
slightly hunched shoulders.
这个女巫到底对我下了什么药啊  莱纳德
What has that vixen done to me, Leonard?
我怎么才能停止这一切呀
And how do I make it stop?
如果你俩有肉体关系的话
Well, if you had a physical relationship,
我会建议你在跟她亲热的过程中求婚
I'd say propose during sex.
绝对一招毙命  性趣全无
Turns out that's a real mood killer.
-我猜咱俩现在聊得是你咯  -没错
- I assume we're talking about you now?  - Yeah.
所以这种社交场合就是这样的吗
So, that's how this works?
我抱怨几句  然后你再接着抱怨几句
I complain, and then you complain,
可大家都没什么解决办法
and no one offers any solutions?
基本上就是这样
Pretty much.
怪不得女人们开始占上风了呢
Well, no wonder the women are winning.
罗森考斯基先生  你在忙吗
Mr. Rostenkowski, are you busy?
我只是在看些老照片  进来吧
Oh, just looking at some old pictures. Come on in.
是家庭照片  还是...
Family pictures, or...?
天哪  那是个死人
H-Holy crap, that's a dead person.
我退休前最后一桩谋杀案
Last murder case before I retired.
这里有多少具死尸
How many bodies do you see there?
好好数
Careful,
这个问题很有难度
it's a trick question.
我不确定
I'm not sure.
算了  你也猜不到
Nah, you'll never get it.
是来自同一尸体的碎块
It's a fraction.
意想不到啊
How about that.
是这样的  先生
Anyway, sir,
我有点事想找你谈谈
I need to talk to you about something.
要吃核桃吗
Walnut?
不用了  谢谢
No, thank you.
我对核桃过敏
I'm allergic.
好的
Oh, sure.
我搭档也过敏
My partner used to have that.
他已经死了
He's dead now.
死于坚果吗[疯子]
From nuts?
不是  被他老婆枪杀的
Nah, his wife shot him.
不过她是疯子  所以某种意义上来说...
But she was nuts, so in a way...
真是好故事
Nice story.
总之
Anyway,
我想跟你谈谈的原因是
the reason I wanted to talk to you is
宇航局把我上太空站的发射提前了
NASA has moved up my launch to the International Space Station.
-那又如何  -那就是说
- Yeah, so? - So...
发射日期跟我娶你女儿的日期有冲突
the date is going to conflict with me marrying your daughter.
我知道你想说什么
Now, I know what you're going to say--
我已对伯纳黛特和您家作出承诺
I made a commitment to Bernadette and to your family
我鼓起万般勇气来到这里
and I've got a hell of a lot of nerve coming in here
提出延期的要求实在是太过分了
and demanding that we postpone this thing.
所以  我明白了也理解了
Well, message heard and understood.
取消去太空站的任务  打扰了
Mission canceled. Thank you.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我可以离开了吗
May I be excused?
不可以
No, you may not.
我来告诉你
Let me tell you something.
我第一次见到你时
When I first met you...
你就站在那里听吗
You just gonna stand there?
抱歉  我不知道  是要...
I'm sorry, I didn't know, is this going to...
好的  我坐下
Well, I should sit...
我能坐吗...我坐下就是
May I be seat... Well, I'll just sit.
我第一次见到你时
When I first met you,
很不喜欢你
I didn't like you.
我知道  先生
I'm aware of that, sir.
跟你相处过一段时间后
But then you and I had some time together.
还是不喜欢你
It did not get better.
好吧
Right, right.
你那愚蠢的披头士发型
That silly Beatle haircut
骑一辆红色小摩托
and...you riding around on a red Vespa,
还跟你妈妈一起住
and you're still living at home with your mother.
老实说  我觉得伯纳黛特选择你
To be honest, I thought Bernadette chose you
是为了惩罚我
to punish me.
然后我听到你要当宇航员的事
But then I heard about your astronaut thing,
我才意识到
and I realized
我过于草率的判断你了
I judged you too fast.
也许你就是最适合我女儿的白马王子
Maybe you are the right guy for my little girl.
我就是  而且你也知道的
Oh, I am. And just so you know,
即使我不去太空了  我也依旧是宇航员
I'd still be an astronaut, even if I didn't go to space.
我有身份认证卡和宇航局的高尔夫衫
I've got an I.D. card and a NASA golf shirt.
不不  你一定得去
No, no, you got to go.
不应该放弃这样的一个机会
You can't turn down an opportunity like this.
那婚礼怎么办
B-But what about the wedding
还有你为婚宴投下去的钱怎么办
and all the money you put down for the reception?
这事我烦恼就好
You let me worry about that.
你安心去那个空间站
You go up to that space station,
让我为你骄傲
and you make me proud.
好吧
Um, okay.
你觉得这有什么问题吗
You got a problem with that?
好吧  我跟你说老实话
All right, look, I'm gonna level with you.
我很害怕进入太空
I'm terrified about going into space.
要是我回不来怎么办
What if I don't make it back?
会没事的  女婿
It's gonna be okay, son.
你真的这么想吗
You really think so?
当然
Of course.
伯纳黛特那么漂亮
A pretty girl like Bernadette...
肯定会找到新归宿
she'll find a new guy.
-去上班吗  -对
- Off to work?  - Yeah.
祝你晚上过得愉快
Have a nice night.
你也是
Okay, you, too.
佩妮  等等
Penny, just, wait.
我一直在想那天
I've been thinking about what I said
我们上床时我说过的话
when we were in bed the other night.
我也一直在想
Yeah, I've been thinking about it, too.
你一直都还没回答我呢
I noticed you never answered me.
没错
You're right.
答案是不
No.
-继续  那我们还是恋人吗  -是啊
- Uh, follow-up. Are we still dating?  - Yep.
-还在因为我求婚而尴尬吗  -是啊
- Is it still weird 'cause I proposed? - Yep.
我还有几个问题要问
I have a couple more quick questions.
-你上车打电话给我谈吧  -别想
- Do you want to call me from the car? - No!
还处理的挺不错嘛
Think I played that pretty well.
你好  莱纳德
Hello, Leonard.
你们在做什么
What are you doing?
我们在玩医生游戏
We're playing doctor.
《星际迷航》式的
Star Trek style.
我堕落了  莱纳德
I'm in hell, Leonard.
别停啊
Don't stop.